<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>thoughts on Yet, another infosec blog</title>
    <link>/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in thoughts on Yet, another infosec blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 10:36:22 +1345</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A README.md</title>
      <link>/posts/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 10:36:22 +1345</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/readme/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal blog where I can share to people my thoughts and experience about (mostly) technology, research articles and sometimes irrelevant stuff.
Topics on this blog are mainly about cyber research, school projects, club tasks or CTF write-ups. I will try to keep the blog updated regularly, one or two posts a week depend on my real life workload.
As some of you have already known that it is not my first blog.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my personal blog where I can share to people my thoughts and experience about (mostly) technology, research articles and sometimes irrelevant stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topics on this blog are mainly about cyber research, school projects, club tasks or CTF write-ups. I will try to keep the blog updated regularly, one or two posts a week depend on my real life workload.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As some of you have already known that it is not my first blog. The reason I created this new one is to improve my English and keeping thing a little bit more professional. I decided that the writing style on this blog will contain concise, research-like materials so you may find it difficult to understand all of the posts, especially my Vietnamese fellows. Please noted that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use any fancy, magic words or try to confuse the readers. The context is still the same, but it will be interpreted in a more academic way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know a lot of people cannot handle the long, visually unstimulating wall-of-text, &lt;em&gt;so do I&lt;/em&gt;. In future posts, many more galleries, formats will be added to make particular topics more interesting and less drowsy for readers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another story which is worth mentioning, now I completely abandoned Medium since Github and Jekyll are doing a great job making blog easier and more customizable. Then why we have to make it harder for ourselves, right? I agree that it is complicated at first but when you are used to it, everything&amp;rsquo;s changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the end of the README on this blog. Have a good day!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
